<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Middle Tennessee's Best Real Estate Training - Monte Mohr</title>
    <description>Monte Mohr, a top Real Estate Agent in Middle Tennessee, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 11:55:51 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 11:55:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: How Do You Build Momentum in Real Estate?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/m_DLVx8fDHk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the key to start selling more than one home per month.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s only one way to get yourself to a place where you’re consistently selling more than one house a month, and that is to &lt;strong&gt;leverage yourself.&lt;/strong&gt; The first time I hired someone to help me with the details (I’m not really a fine-details kind of guy), I saw my business &lt;em&gt;double.&lt;/em&gt; Originally, I didn’t think I could afford the cost of help, but then I realized that I was already incurring the cost myself while simultaneously inhibiting my growth. Investing in help was the right call.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Your excellence is in serving the local person who knows, likes, and trusts you.%20http://localhost:4000/q-how-do-you-build-momentum-in-real-estate.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Your excellence is in serving the local person who knows, likes, and trusts you.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a big advocate of using a local company here called Contract to Close. Toni White is the owner (her number is 615-289-1452), and I honestly don’t know what I’d do without her. I know it may seem odd that I’m spending my time and money promoting a business that gives me nothing in return for doing so, but &lt;strong&gt;I believe in the need to walk in excellence as a real estate professional; get the things that you’re not great at off of your plate. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Handing off the details frees up more time for you to do the things that you’re excellent at—or that you need to &lt;em&gt;become&lt;/em&gt; excellent at anyhow. Remember: Your excellence is in serving the local person who knows, likes, and trusts you, whether you’re helping them buy or sell, or just locate the best painter in town. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’re doing the details, you’re never going to get off the ground.&lt;/strong&gt; Momentum is the secret to this business, and you will never achieve it if you insist on controlling all of the details. Even if you’re a control freak like me, you need to let go of those things that you really don’t need to have your hand on. Let someone who’s a professional in that area handle it. Did you know there are somewhere between 18 and 20 hours of details in every transaction? Imagine all of the things you could be doing with that time to grow your business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you grow your business, you’re becoming more proficient at what you do, and that means you’re able to be better for those who need you most. How can you expect to become excellent at something if you’re only doing it a couple of times throughout the year? If you help somebody buy a home and hand off the details to someone like Toni at Contract to Close, you’ll be able to jump right back into helping some other couple or family find a home and build momentum. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stop sinking time on the tasks that you could delegate to someone else who will do them better—because that’s &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; they do. I recommend seeking out a local contract-to-close professional; it’s the best way to start freeing up your time and reducing unnecessary stress. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a Realtor looking for strategies to succeed, please reach out to me with questions or examples of problem areas you’re facing. I’d love to help. You can call me at 615-925-0204, or send an email. Our new 5,400-square-foot office will soon be open in Berry Hill, and it’s an awesome and convenient location. I look forward to hearing from you. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 10:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-how-do-you-build-momentum-in-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-how-do-you-build-momentum-in-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: How Do You Stay Connected With Your Database?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/AeiWd6RbbW8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s what I do to let my database know that I’m always here for them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a non-competing broker but still an active one, and that’s because &lt;strong&gt;I have a conviction that I can be of far greater value to my agents if I’m still out there experiencing the pains of our current market&lt;/strong&gt;—not a market I knew five, 10, or 15 years ago. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone in this industry strives to stay top-of-mind for a database of people who know, like, and trust them. What I’ve found to be &lt;strong&gt;one of the most effective and simplest ways to follow up with your database is to drop folks a postcard.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The last thing you want to do is give somebody something that has no value.%20http://localhost:4000/q-how-do-you-stay-connected-with-your-database.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The last thing you want to do is give somebody something that has no value.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are different approaches to postcard content (i.e., recipes, recent listings, quotes, etc.), but I find it useful to think about it as a time issue: people will be walking from the mailbox to the garbage can, so what can I see in a matter of a few seconds that will grab their attention? I choose to say something inspirational, like the following:  “Success is no accident. It is hard work, perseverance, learning, studying, sacrifice, and most of all, a love of what you’re doing.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I choose this route to hit that part of a person’s brain that suggests to them that this is a positive encounter with me; on the back of the postcard, I have a picture of myself, a call to action, an engaging question, and a message of gratitude. It’s basic, but enables me to stay top of mind without hitting people over the head all of the time with some exhausted plea. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last thing you want to do is give somebody something that has no value. &lt;strong&gt;Given the world today, most people are always thankful to receive some meaningful inspiration.&lt;/strong&gt; In addition to postcards, I’ll often write a personalized note—something simple, like, “Hey Bob and Sally, just want to let you know I appreciate you.” These are the little things that enable me to sell two to three homes per month on autopilot mode; I stay on people’s minds and leave a feeling of positivity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a real estate professional stuck in a tough spot, please reach out. I’ve sold thousands of homes, so if there’s a decent chance I could shine a light on your situation, I’d love to help. Give me a call at 615-925-0204 or send an email any time, and remember: we’re the office that provides 100% commission on top of everything else that a real estate agent would want.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 11:47:54 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-how-do-you-stay-connected-with-your-database.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-how-do-you-stay-connected-with-your-database.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Winning the Battle Between Your Ears</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fe_eX9WnssQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;How do you become a billion-dollar broker? The first step is winning the battle between your ears.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other day, someone said to me, “Monte, I’m new in the business and I want to become a billion-dollar broker like you. What do I do?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=At the end of the day, we have to own what’s decided in our heads.%20http://localhost:4000/winning-the-battle-between-your-ears.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“At the end of the day, we have to own what’s decided in our heads.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I paused for a second and thought that I couldn’t really credit anything other than longevity in the industry. Throughout my 36 years in the business, I’ve been truly committed to it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I kept going back to this question, though, and I think the most important step is &lt;strong&gt;winning the battle between your ears.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s easy to blame something on the economy, our political leadership, or a global pandemic, but at the end of the day, we have to own what’s decided in our heads. Are you going to win that battle? How do you win that battle?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe you win it by &lt;strong&gt;keeping yourself fed with the &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;information.&lt;/strong&gt; For example, one of my favorite books of all time is “The Prosperity Battle,” which is a compilation of 18 of the best books ever written about prosperity. The first book is “Think and Grow Rich,” by Napoleon Hill—an absolute classic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to become a billion-dollar broker, be committed in your heart of hearts to winning the battle between your ears and feed yourself with positive information. Stay focused on that. Continue to love and honor people and put others’ needs above your own. After that, hang on for one of the craziest rides of your life because you have the opportunity to make a difference on this planet and become who you’re destined to be. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish you luck, and remember: I’m here to serve you if I can help you with your real estate career. If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 12:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/winning-the-battle-between-your-ears.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/winning-the-battle-between-your-ears.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I Want to Share My Expertise &amp; Experience With You</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VE_LK-z_ZgY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you need a lifeline, I’m here to help. Here’s how.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The situation in real estate right now is pretty crazy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we speak, hundreds of agents are deactivating their licenses because the business has gotten tougher. This is to be expected, though, because a chunk of the population in our industry isn’t fully committed to it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that in mind, I have a simple message to share with you: &lt;strong&gt;Before the message matters, people have to believe the messenger.&lt;/strong&gt; I’ve been doing this for 36 years. I’ve sold over $1 billion in volume and have helped over 3,000 families buy or sell homes. Though I’m not a competing broker with the other agents in my office, I’m still an active broker, and part of the reason is that I want to feel the pain of the market in today’s world and be relevant to our agents. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=I want to do my part to elevate the expertise in our industry and raise the bar.%20http://localhost:4000/i-want-to-share-my-expertise-experience-with-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“I want to do my part to elevate the expertise in our industry and raise the bar.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On that note, &lt;strong&gt;I want to share my expertise and experience with other local agents in the area who are perhaps in need of a lifeline.&lt;/strong&gt; Maybe you don’t feel certain about a listing’s value, or you’re not sure what to do about a certain situation. I’m not saying I have all the answers, but I want to do my part to elevate the expertise in our industry and raise the bar. Specifically, I want to help you convey your value to the consumer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, prosperity follows value. If you want to make more in any business, you have to become more. Right now, business probably isn’t as busy as you’d like it to be, so it’s a great opportunity to become an expert in every topic that resonates with who you are. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hang in there, and keep doing what you do best. If there’s anything I can do to help you, call my cell at (615) 300-8393. I won’t take on any liability, but I am taking on the care and concern of the expertise in our industry so I can help you raise the bar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any other questions, feel free to reach out to me as well. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 12:38:08 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/i-want-to-share-my-expertise-experience-with-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/i-want-to-share-my-expertise-experience-with-you.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Be Blessed By Helping Others</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BbzM8IwDYiY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;During a difficult time in my life, I acquired a hunger for learning. I&amp;rsquo;m sharing that story and the book that helped me do it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I want to share how I received my hunger for learning. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things weren’t great in my life at one time: &lt;strong&gt;I was a laid-off factory worker who qualified for food stamps.&lt;/strong&gt; One evening I went to church and a gentleman in our congregation who knew I was having a difficult time handed me a $100 bill and said: “Monte, go buy yourself a new pair of shoes.” He’d noticed my socks were hanging out of the bottom of my current pair. He also handed me a book called “See You at the Top,” by Zig Ziglar. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You’ll be blessed if you help others.%20http://localhost:4000/be-blessed-by-helping-others.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You’ll be blessed if you help others.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve talked about some of the books that have changed my life before, but this was the first one. The main thing I learned from “See You at the Top” is that if you simply help enough people get what they’re searching for in life, you’ll certainly get what you’re searching for. &lt;strong&gt;You’ll be blessed if you help others. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Becoming a billion-dollar real estate broker has been quite a journey—it took me 36 years. I often say that you must win the battle in your own mind before anything else can happen for you. My goal is to help real estate agents succeed sooner than I did. I believe that &lt;strong&gt;success leaves clues,&lt;/strong&gt; and those of us who have found it can help others find it too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I can ever assist you with your real estate needs, please call or email me. Let me be your lifeline if you’re in a real estate transaction you don’t know how to navigate. I would love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 14:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/be-blessed-by-helping-others.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/be-blessed-by-helping-others.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why You Should Read “The Miracle Morning for Real Estate Agents”</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6MCWQ3SOUjo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;When I read &amp;ldquo;The Miracle Morning for Real Estate Agents,&amp;rdquo; it changed my life and career. It can do the same for you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two years ago, I read a book entitled “The Miracle Morning for Real Estate Agents: It’s Your Time to Rise and Shine” by Hal Elrod, Michael J. Maher, and Michael Reese. At the age of 67, I can tell you that my life changed when I read it and started applying its lessons to my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The wisdom in this book is incredible.%20http://localhost:4000/why-you-should-read-the-miracle-morning-for-real-estate-agents.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The wisdom in this book is incredible.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One memorable aspect of the book was the acronym SAVERS, which stands for:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;• Silence&lt;/strong&gt;: Meditation. Prayer. Breathing. Whatever it is for you, the idea is to quiet your mind and block out the noise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;• Affirmations&lt;/strong&gt;: Write down encouraging words to help you achieve your goals, overcome your fears, be healthy, and find success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;• Visualization&lt;/strong&gt;: Visualize your business as you want to see it. Visualize qualified, motivated, appreciative, and coachable clients coming to you for business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;• Exercise&lt;/strong&gt;: Make sure that you get some type of exercise, even if it’s only for five or 10 minutes each morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;• Reading&lt;/strong&gt;: Read plenty of books and other materials like “The Miracle Morning” to take in as much good advice as possible and to hone your thought process for success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;• Scribing&lt;/strong&gt;: Take some time to write down what’s in your heart and mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wisdom in this book is incredible, and I can’t recommend it enough. If you’d like to receive a free copy or have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be happy to send you one so you can start implementing its life-changing tips in your own business.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 11:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-you-should-read-the-miracle-morning-for-real-estate-agents.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/why-you-should-read-the-miracle-morning-for-real-estate-agents.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ribbon Home Program: A New Way to Buy &amp; Sell at the Same Time</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/19O4J0FdkR0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a new way to help clients buy a new home and sell their old one: Ribbon Homes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my experience, contingent offers don’t typically fly with sellers. In a hot market, most homeowners don’t want to put their eggs in another person’s basket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;That’s why I’m grateful for a new company in town called Ribbon Homes, which can help take care of the stress of selling a home while also trying to buy a new one.&lt;/strong&gt; In the past, we’d advise people to put their homes on the market first, and they’d typically have two or three weeks to find a replacement home to buy. This way, they could round out both transactions at roughly the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now, Ribbon Homes does it a little differently&lt;/strong&gt;. After you get an approval letter from your lender, you can go out and choose your new home without the pressure of having to sell another home. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=I’m a true believer in this system because I know what it has done for our clients.%20http://localhost:4000/ribbon-home-program-a-new-way-to-buy-sell-at-the-same-time.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“I’m a true believer in this system because I know what it has done for our clients.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How? &lt;strong&gt;Well, Ribbon will pay cash for the new home you chose, closing in a time frame that works for you, which will allow you to move into that home on a temporary rental basis&lt;/strong&gt;—up to six months, if needed.  If there’s a concern about cash flow on the front end, they’ll be able to defer those rent payments. They’ll then be able to better prepare your current home by staging it properly so they get the highest value possible when you do sell it. Once Ribbon closes on the new home, they’ll be able to sell it to the client for the price they purchased it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is a 2% fee to do it this way,&lt;/strong&gt; but it can also help clients avoid the negative associations sellers have with contingency offers and the pressure of having to buy and sell a home at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing I like most about the Ribbon program is that &lt;strong&gt;it empowers us as real estate professionals.&lt;/strong&gt; They don’t try to go behind our backs like so many companies out there. They pay a fair market price, they close quickly, and it’s convenient for the clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a true believer in this system because I know what it has done for our clients. In the last 30 days, I sold five homes for sellers who wouldn’t have been able to buy a new home without the Ribbon Home program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the program, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ribbonhome.com&quot;&gt;www.RibbonHome.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For any other real estate needs you have, don’t hesitate to reach out to us at the RealtyOne Group. We’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 15:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/ribbon-home-program-a-new-way-to-buy-sell-at-the-same-time.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/ribbon-home-program-a-new-way-to-buy-sell-at-the-same-time.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Foolproof Method to Maximize Listings</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yDBQeieOVcA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve found that what separates &amp;ldquo;just okay&amp;rdquo; listings from the top, buzz-generating listings can be boiled down to the eight things I&amp;rsquo;m sharing with you today.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been in the real estate business for over 35 years, and during that time I’ve helped over 3,000 families with their real estate needs. Over the years, I developed a nearly foolproof technique to maximize a home’s value and capture an additional two to three buyers on almost every listing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the eight steps that I’ve integrated into my approach: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price for attention.&lt;/strong&gt; There cannot be any doubt in the buyer’s mind when the walk in the home that it’s priced correctly. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get a professional photographer in for pictures by Wednesday.&lt;/strong&gt; Doing this will mean you can get those stellar photos back by Friday, just in time to entice weekend shoppers. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Activate the listing Friday.&lt;/strong&gt; There are ten times as many eyeballs peering over listings on Friday afternoon than any other time of the week. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create fear of loss.&lt;/strong&gt; Here’s the tricky part: Do not let anyone see the home for the next nine days after the listing goes active. Then, on that Sunday, hold a mega open house. Keep buyers thinking that your home could go off the market at any time. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get your open house signs up.&lt;/strong&gt; Do this one week from when the listing goes active, and make sure you saturate the area—open house signs on every corner! &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More signs, more attention.&lt;/strong&gt; That following Sunday, put even more signs out, this time with balloons attached. Do whatever you can to make the open house experience seem special and interesting. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get a partner.&lt;/strong&gt; Make sure you have a partner with you; when people try to capture everyone on their own, they end up capturing no one. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a hook.&lt;/strong&gt; What is your simple, quick line to say that best encapsulates all the features of your house that buyers will find attractive? Find it, know it, use it, repeat it. Speak to the paying points. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for me about this list or about anything else in general, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 12:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-foolproof-method-to-maximize-listings.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-foolproof-method-to-maximize-listings.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Maximize Your Listings That Might Upset The Competition</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been in the real estate business for over 35 years, and during that time I’ve helped over 3,000 families with their real estate needs. Over the years, I developed a nearly full-proof technique to maximize a home’s value and capture an additional two to three buyers on almost every listing. For example, do you know the exact time you should activate your listing? To learn about my eight proven steps, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yDBQeieOVcA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the eight steps that I’ve integrated into my approach: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price for attention.&lt;/strong&gt; There cannot be any doubt in the buyer’s mind when the walk in the home that it’s priced correctly. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get a professional photographer in for pictures by Wednesday.&lt;/strong&gt; Doing this will mean you can get those stellar photos back by Friday, just in time to entice weekend shoppers. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Activate the listing Friday.&lt;/strong&gt; There are ten times as many eyeballs peering over listings on Friday afternoon than any other time of the week. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create fear of loss.&lt;/strong&gt; Here’s the tricky part: Do not let anyone see the home for the next nine days after the listing goes active. Then, on the following Sunday, hold a mega open house. This is a critical part of this. Remember you are creating the greatest influence in the world: the fear of loss. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get your open house signs up.&lt;/strong&gt; On the Friday before the open house, start putting your open house signs up. Make sure you saturate the area—open house signs on every corner! &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More signs, more attention.&lt;/strong&gt; That following Sunday, put even more signs out, this time with balloons attached. Do whatever you can to make the open house experience seem special and interesting. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get a partner.&lt;/strong&gt; Make sure you have a partner with you; when people try to capture everyone on their own, they end up capturing no one. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a hook.&lt;/strong&gt; Create a hook that speaks to a pain point of people walking in to the house.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did a longer training going further in depth about these 8 steps, and also made a PDF that you can download. Watch my training and download the PDF &lt;a href=&quot;/uploads/listing.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;/uploads/listing.pdf&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;1000px&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-maximize-your-listings-that-might-upset-the-competition.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-maximize-your-listings-that-might-upset-the-competition.html</guid>
        
        <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Maximize Your Listings That Might Upset the Competition</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been in the real estate business for over 35 years, and during that time I’ve helped over 3,000 families with their real estate needs. Over the years, I developed a nearly full-proof technique to maximize a home’s value and capture an additional two to three buyers on almost every listing. For example, do you know the exact time you should activate your listing? To learn about my eight proven steps, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/R-zC_vTCfTo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the eight steps that I’ve integrated into my approach: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price for attention.&lt;/strong&gt; There cannot be any doubt in the buyer’s mind when the walk in the home that it’s priced correctly. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get a professional photographer in for pictures by Wednesday.&lt;/strong&gt; Doing this will mean you can get those stellar photos back by Friday, just in time to entice weekend shoppers. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Activate the listing Friday.&lt;/strong&gt; There are ten times as many eyeballs peering over listings on Friday afternoon than any other time of the week. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create fear of loss.&lt;/strong&gt; Here’s the tricky part: Do not let anyone see the home for the next nine days after the listing goes active. Then, on the following Sunday, hold a mega open house. This is a critical part of this. Remember you are creating the greatest influence in the world: the fear of loss. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/how-to-maximize-your-listings-that-might-upset-the-competition.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get your open house signs up.&lt;/strong&gt; On the Friday before the open house, start putting your open house signs up. Make sure you saturate the area—open house signs on every corner! &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More signs, more attention.&lt;/strong&gt; That following Sunday, put even more signs out, this time with balloons attached. Do whatever you can to make the open house experience seem special and interesting. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get a partner.&lt;/strong&gt; Make sure you have a partner with you; when people try to capture everyone on their own, they end up capturing no one. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a hook.&lt;/strong&gt; Create a hook that speaks to a pain point of people walking in to the house. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can &lt;a href=&quot;/uploads/listing.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;download the free PDF by clicking here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;/uploads/listing.pdf&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;1000px&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-maximize-your-listings-that-might-upset-the-competition.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-maximize-your-listings-that-might-upset-the-competition.html</guid>
        
        <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <category>Free Training</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
